(Bernadette:)Do you know he once got
an asthma attack...
(Bernadette:)...from reading an old library book?
- You're kidding.
- No, I was there that day.
(Penny:)Sheldon threw his back out
handing him that book.
(Bernadette:)I don't know what I'm going to do.
(Bernadette:)I don't want to break up over this.
Why don't you tell him
you made a mistake?
(Bernadette:)Do you guys think it was a mistake?
(Bernadette:)Am I the bad guy in this?
It's not for us to judge. We're here
to provide comfort and support...
(Amy:)...while you come to grips with
what a despicable thing you've done.
(Bernadette:)Oh, God, you're right.
(Bernadette:)I took our love and
threw it under his bus-sized mother.
(Bernadette:)- I need to apologize.
- That's good, I'm glad you came to that.
(Penny:)But before you do, let me just
ask you a big picture question.
(Bernadette:)What?
(Penny:)Are you a hundred percent positive
you love...